TINA PARK

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

213-435-4947 | tuna.park@gmail.com | Los Angeles, CA tinasunpark.com | github.com/gebigoma | linkedin.com/in/tina-sun-park

SUMMARY:

I am a full stack developer proficient in MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node) and Ruby on Rails. I also have experience starting up small businesses from the ground up. Currently I am working on an app using React that aggregates original sugar-free recipes from health conscious food bloggers from around the world.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node), JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Active Admin, RESTful API, Axios, EJS, JSX, JWT, Passport, Bcrypt, Amazon S3, Semantic-UI-CSS, Semantic-UI-React, Bootstrap, Bulma, HTML5, CSS3, WordPress, Heroku, Git

PROJECTS:

Sugarfree Gallery

An aggregate site of original recipes submitted by healthy bloggers from around the world.

Technologies used: React.js | Node.js | Mongoose | MongoDB | Express | RESTful API | Axios | JSX | JWT | Amazon S3 | Semantic-UI-CSS | Semantic-UI-React | JavaScript | HTMLS | CSS3 | Heroku

Surf Buddy

Surf Buddy bridges surfers and their experiences of all the best spots in California. On-site feedback is the best indicator of current conditions.

Technologies used: JavaScript | Node.js | Mongoose | MongoDB | Express | RESTful API | Axios | EJS | Passport.js | Method-Override | Semantics UI | Spitcase API | HTML5 | CSS3 | Heroku

Campsite Findr

A crowdsourced app where users can submit details about a campsite they visited. Submit an image, the location, and also review the sites!

Technologies used: Ruby on Rails | PostgreSQL | Active Admin | Bcrypt | HTML5 | CSS | SASS | Bootstrap HTML | Google Font | Font Awesome | Heroku

Dream Recall

This is a 2 player memory game. Users are must match the gifs they are first shown with a series of gifs on the next screen. Then Player 2 takes their turn and the best score wins!

Technologies used: Vanilla JavaScript | jQuery | HTML5 | CSS | Google Fonts | Giphy Gifs

EXPERIENCE:

POJANG KOREAN FOOD, Owner & Chef

2014 - 2015

- Startup business with minimal funds, no loans or investors. Turned profit within 3 months of opening. Implemented efficient kitchen flow to minimize waste.

WILSHIRE STATE BANK, Business Banking Specialist

2007 - 2013

- Series 6 licensed banking specialist. Consulted clients for variable annuities. Trained and supervised employees.

MOD INDUSTRIES, Sample Coordinator

2002-2006

- Managed high-end denim client's sample production. Coordinated work flow between factory, vendors, pattern makers, and the designer. Responsible for meeting production deadlines.

EDUCATION:

General Assembly, Web Development Immersive (12 weeks)

2018